Finding Aid of the WUWM Records, 1950-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
WUWM Records, 1950-2014
WUWM (Radio Station: Milwaukee, Wis.)
UWM Archival Collection 2
Accession 2006-024
Accession 2007-038
9.4 cubic ft. (17 boxes, including 227 audio reels and 161 audio cassettes) 398 digital audio files (96.2 GB) plus additions of 0.5 cubic ft. (1 box and 1 folder)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records of the WUWM public radio station and the Mass Communication Department of UWM. Includes correspondence and subject files of WUWM concerning the programming, financing and technical needs of the station, and records of the Mass Communication Department documenting its relationship to the radio station as well as the curricular and publication activities of the department. Audio tape recordings of the College Talk, Grass Roots, East Side Issues, and miscellaneous programs document opinions and political campaigns of public officials, including Lloyd Barbee, John Doyne, Warren Knowles, Gaylord Nelson, Henry Reuss, and Clement Zablocki. The collection also includes a recording of Robert Kennedy speaking at a political rally for Patrick Lucey at UWM's Baker Field House on September 17, 1966. A number of recordings concern conditions and policies at Wisconsin prisons. The most recent addition to the collection consists of recordings of four UWM-related programs, University Roundtable, Milwaukee Ideas, UWM Today, and Chancellor's Report. These programs featured issues of interest to the UWM and Milwaukee community, such as electoral campaigns and college affordability, as well as updates on happenings at UWM itself.
The Journalism Department originated in 1951 as a minor within the English Department of the Wisconsin State College, Milwaukee. By 1954, it was a separate department headed by Professor Harold N. Ahlgren. In 1963, the department began the WUWM public radio station to provide students with laboratory experience. The Journalism Department changed its name in 1970 to the Mass Communication Department. In 1975, the Mass Communication Department hired professionals to staff the full-time positions at WUWM.
The emphasis of the Mass Communication Department throughout its existence was to provide students with the education for careers in mass communication while offering opportunities for students to work in privately and publicly owned radio stations and newspapers. The Mass Communication Department maintained close ties with WUWM and students still continue to work part-time for the station.
As of 2016, WUWM is operated by UWM's College of Letters and Science, and the Director/General Manager of the station reports directly to the Dean of the College.
Collection contains records created by the Mass Communication Department and public radio station WUWM of the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. The records of the Dept. of Mass Communication (series 1) contain correspondence of the department chair (1951-1976) documenting the creation of the department, its goals, and activities such as the curriculum, staffing and policy needs. It also includes minutes of the executive committee (1970-1979) and faculty meeting minutes (1970-1974).
The WUWM General Files (series 2) document station programming and, to a lesser extent, the staffing and technical needs of the station. The correspondence of the director (1963-1983) provides details on the operations and activities of the station including equipment purchases, staffing needs, policy decisions and employee relations. For example, some 1969 letters to the dean of the College of Letters and Science concern controversies after profane language had been used on the air. The station director's memos also document the policies and the needs of the station for 1978 and 1979. One folder contains information on African American programs on the station, and a series of folders documents the station's financial and programming connections to the Corporation for Public Broadcasting.
Series 3-10 include audio reel recordings of the College Talk program, the Grass Roots program, the East Side Issues program, the University Roundtable program, the Milwaukee Ideas program, the UWM Today program, the Chancellor's Report, and other miscellaneous programs. The tapes were recorded at varying speeds and are organized by sequential numbers. Most of the audio reels are from the Grass Roots program, which covered local Milwaukee politics between 1964 and 1966. The host interviewed public officials, including Lloyd Barbee, John Doyne, Warren Knowles, Gaylord Nelson, Henry Reuss, and Clement Zablocki. Tape 117 is a recording of Robert F. Kennedy speaking at a political rally for Patrick Lucey at UWM's Baker Field House on September 17, 1966. A number of recordings concern conditions and policies at Wisconsin prisons. A College Talk program tape includes interviews with African American families concerning the housing situation in Milwaukee in 1969.
The University Roundtable, Milwaukee Ideas and UWM Today recordings cover a mixture of UWM-specific topics, reports on faculty research, and current events interpreted by UWM faculty and staff. University Roundtable, the earliest of these, took the form of conversations between Station manager Dave Edwards and Chancellors John Schroeder and Nancy Zimpher, and discussed topics such as Sexual Discrimination awareness on campus, the state budget and its effect on UWM, and the UWM Basketball program. These programs were not preserved in their full runs; much of 1996-1999 is not represented at all in this collection.
The later programs moved to a weekly schedule and are much more comprehensive, though gaps in the collection do still exist. Specific topics from these shows include the Peck School of the Arts performance schedule for the upcoming year, discussion of local and national political races, an overview by Prof. Barry Rousseau of his research in volcanology, updates on UWM student community-building in New Orleans post-Katrina, and UWM Athletics previews. Of particular interest are Chancellor Nancy Zimpher's discussion of UWM's response to the 9/11/2001 terrorist attacks, as well as the large number of Freshwater Studies-related programs, which describe the work being done by the Great Lakes WATER Institute and, after 2009, the School of Freshwater Studies.
The Chancellor's Report recordings, which span over both Milwaukee Ideas and UWM Today, served as a monthly forum for the Chancellor to publicly discuss the issues facing their office and UWM as a whole, and provide an excellent month-to-month summary of the Chancellor's activities and what they considered important that month. Recordings are present in the collection from Chancellors Nancy Zimpher (1998-2003), Carlos Santiago (2004-2010), and Michael Lovell (2010-2014). The records of the Office of the Chancellor (UWM Archival Collection 46) contain program notes and supplementary materials for many of these recordings, after 2003 in electronic format.
The records are arranged into the following ten series:
Dept. of Mass Communication, 1950-1991
WUWM General Files, 1963-1983
WUWM College Talk, 1967-1970
WUWM Grass Roots, 1964-1967
WUWM Miscellaneous Programs, 1974-1975
WUWM East Side Issues, 1977-1982
WUWM University Roundtable, 1991-2001
WUWM Milwaukee Ideas, 2002-2004
WUWM UWM Today, 2005-2012
WUWM Chancellor's Report, 2001-2014
Series 1-5 are organized alphabetically by subject or title of program. Series 6-10 are organized chronologically by date of broadcast.
Electronic recordings in series 8-10 are organized by folder, with one program per folder. The ID number for each recording corresponds to the folder title on the Archives department server.
The collection consists of two additional accessions:
Accession 2006-024: Miscellaneous Recordings, 1964-1965
Accession 2007-038: Chancellor Baum Retirement Materials, 1979
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
UW-Milwaukee College of Letters & Science, Office of the Dean Records UWM Archival Collection 1
UW-Milwaukee Dept. of Mass Communications Records UWM Archival Collection 179
UW-Milwaukee Office of the Chancellor Records UWM Archival Collection 46
UW-Milwaukee University Relations Records UWM Archival Collection 96
A list of the UWM Today and Chancellor's Report CDs that were not successfully transferred to digital format is available in the Archives. Also available is a spreadsheet of information about the digital files, including date created, duration, and embedded information about show subjects and guests. See an archivist for more information.
Administrative/Restriction Information
Electronic audio files in the collection must be accessed on computers in the Archives. Contact an archivist for more information.
There are no other access restrictions on the materials, and the collection is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
Professor Ruane Hill transferred 10 cubic feet on May 26, 1976. Another unknown donor transferred 1 cubic feet on August 15, 1976 and 5 cubic feet of WUWM logs on November 17, 1976. William Moritz transferred the audio tapes on October 1, 1980. The East Side Issues tapes were added in November 1995. Doug Freshner donated materials in 2006 (Accession 2006-024) and 2008 (Accession 2007-038). University Relations transferred CDs and audio cassettes of Milwaukee Ideas and UWM Today in August 2009 (Accession 2009-007) and August 2012 (Accession 2012-012). The Office of the Chancellor transferred CDs and audio cassettes of University Roundtable and Chancellor's Report in September 2012 (Accession 2012-023) and electronic files of programs in July 2014 (Accession 2014-004).
As of September 7, 2016, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core i5-4570 CPU (3.20 GHz, 4 GB RAM) running Windows 7 Enterprise, with Service Pack 1. Windows Media Player was used to access the files.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Broadcast Wave File [.wav]
MPEG Audio Layer 3 [.mp3]
Contents List
- WUWM Records, 1950-2014, UWM Archival Collection 2; 9.4 cubic ft. (17 boxes, including 227 audio reels and 161 audio cassettes) 398 digital audio files (96.2 GB)
  - 1. Dept. of Mass Communication, 1950-1991
    - Correspondence, 1950-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Course and Curriculum Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Curriculum Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee, 1956, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Joint Conference Committee, 1956-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Mass Comm Scanner, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Mass Communication Forums, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Masters Program, 1963-1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Policies and Actions, 1951-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Publications, 1965, 1970, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Schwandner Scholarship, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Urban Journalism Workshop, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Workshops and Conferences, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2. WUWM General Files, 1963-1983
    - Ad Hoc Review Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Advisory Board, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - African American Programming, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Antenna and Licensing, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Audience and Self-Study Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Awards, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Blind Programming, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Capitol Ideas Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 24-27)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting
      - Annual Financial Report, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Community Service Project and Information Survey, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Facilities Survey, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Incentive Grant Fiscal Report, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Occupancy Value Revisions, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Radio Content Survey, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Survey, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 34-35)
    - Director's Correspondence, 1963-1983 (Box 1, Folder 36-39)
    - Director's Memos, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Division of Urban Outreach, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Emergency Broadcast System, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Program, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - FCC Annual Employment Report, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Fifth Anniversary, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Friends of WUWM
      - 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Steering Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - General Office Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Grants, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - History, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Insight Series, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Jazz Programming, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Latino Training Program, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Legal Problems, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Listener's Surveys, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - National Association of Educational Broadcasters, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - National Educational Radio Minimum Criteria Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Native American Trainee Position, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - News Bulletins, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Options in Education, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Pledgefest, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Policy Statements on Students, Programming, and Personnel, 1974, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Program Guides, 1965-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    - Rapport Afro-America Controversy, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Recruitment, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Sounds of Yesterday, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Spanish Programming, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Spanish Speaking Community, 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Staff Meetings, 1963-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
    - Tenth Anniversary, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Wingspread Conference for Education and Broadcasters, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Wisconsin Broadcasters Association, 1964-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - Wisconsin Public Journal, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Wisconsin Women Artists Program, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Women in the Humanities, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - You are on Indian Land Series, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 3. WUWM College Talk, 1967-1970
    - Afro-American Studies, with Willie Box and Liedan Landuyt, November 15, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Beer on Campuses, with Richard C. Langer and Andrew Schmeibing, January 10, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Birth Control, with Mike Kurth, Manoon Inbanputr, Elayne Mattson, and Linda Schmelling, February 14, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Drugs: Their Use and Abuse, with Gary Davies and Cameron Smith, January 3, 1967, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - Generation Gap, with Cynthia Lauber and Barry Mano, December 20, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Governmental Reform, Mayor Wallace E. Burkee, F. James Mitchell and Dennis Conti, November 15, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hippie Look, April 4, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Invasion of Privacy, with Doren Van Konigsveld, Walter Christofferson and Carthage Students, February 7, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lowering the Voting Age: Pros and Cons, with Phillip Simpson as Moderator, Barton, Might, Ulbricht, March 6, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Military Draft, with Guy Sturino and Ray Bohm, December 6, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Minority vs. Majority, Part 3, undated, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Minority vs. Majority, with Isom Flann as Moderator, George Thomas, Pat Tilley, November 29, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Peaceful or Militant, November 1, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Pollution, with LaFollette, Dory, Alfred Krampert, Barry Jones, January 17, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
    - Right to Dissent, with Todd Munson, Kathy Shulz and Carthage College, January 31, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Sexual Revolution, with Geoffrey Fox, Monica Tutka, Colleen Stone, Burner, Perry Michalos and John Frederick, February 21, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Student Voice in Campus Affair, with Allen Dearborn, Jim Smith, Marc Colby, November 8, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Troops from Vietnam, October, 25, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - U.N.: How it Can Be Made More Effective, with Dr. Roger Hambury, Ann Schulz and John Gothfredsen, February 27, 1970, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - War Moratoriums, with Tom Knight, Bill Smith and Mike Lofton, December 13, 1969, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 4. WUWM Grass Roots, 1964-1967
    - Aetherius Society, with Dr. George King, President, Summer 1967, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - African American Family Interviews, April 30, 1964, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Alcoholism Special, September 26, 1965, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 23-28)
    - Anatomy of a Delinquent, with Coffey, Tilton, Kegel, Paakratz, February 16, 1966, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 31-33)
    - Assembly District 1 Race, with Mark Lipscomb and Herb Schollmeyer, October 6, 1966, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 34-35)
    - Assembly District 2 Race, with Joseph E. Jones, October 4, 1966, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 36-37)
    - Assembly District 3, with Joseph F. Bellante, August 25, 1966, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Assembly District 5, with Finch, Christopher, Schaus, Secala, August 9, 1967, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Assembly District 6, with Lloyd Barbee, August 11, 1966, Audio reel (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Assembly District 9, with Mertz, Jackson, Larson and Montag, August 23, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Assembly District 10 Race, with Kessler, Fred, October 20, 1967, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 42-43)
    - Assembly District 11, with Tobiaz and Means, September 29, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
    - Assembly District 12 Race, with Pinowarczyk, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Assembly District 13 Race, with Elmer Kurtz, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 47-48)
    - Assembly District 14, with Koniecki and Zablocki, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Assembly District 15, with McCann and Van Hyle, September 22, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
    - Assembly District 16, with Pabst, Burt, etc., 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 52-53)
    - Assembly District 17 Race, with John McCormick, October 13, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 54-55)
    - Assembly District 18, with Held, Stude, August 9, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Assembly District 19, with Carlson, Ward, Dobbs and Hanna, August 23, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Assembly District 20 Race, with George Klicka, September 7, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Assembly District 21, with James R. Cooper and Charlotte Snyder, August 18, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Assembly District 22, with Robert T. Huber, October 18, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 60-61)
    - Assembly District 23 Race, with James C. Devitt and Thomas Grap, August 30, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Assembly District 24 Race, with William P. Atkinson, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Assembly District 25, with William S. Weiner, October 11, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 64-65)
    - Attorney General Race, with Louis Ceici, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 66-67)
    - Baldwin and O'Donnell - Milwaukee County Welfare: Its Services, Its Budget and You, May 18, 1965, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 68-69)
    - Carley, Dave - Press Conference, January 30, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Carley, Dave - Press Conference, undated, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Children's Court, with Judge Howard Brown, April 19, 1966, Audio reel (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Children's Court, with Judge Howard Brown, April 19, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Children's Court Race, with Brown, Bouman, Tilton, etc., Spring 1967, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 74-75)
    - Circuit Court Clerk Race, with E. Curtis Rogers, October 25, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Congressional District 4 Race, with James Laessie 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Congressional District 5, with Reuss and Pechtel, September 6, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Congressional District 9 Race, with Jim Buckley, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - County Purchasing Department, with Lydia Stetz, November 30, 1965, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Court Branch 10 Race, with Koch and Fiorenza, Spring 1967, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 81-82)
    - Criminal Court, with Judge Herbet J. Steffes, April 19, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 83-84)
    - Currier, Ruth, June 28, 1965, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Davies, Glenn R., December 7, 1965, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Democratic State Convention, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 87-88)
    - Democratic Fund Raising, undated, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - District Attorney Mary Doyle, May 10, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 90-91)
    - District Attorney Race, with Darryl Nevers, November 3, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 92-93)
    - District Judge Race, with Ceici, October, 5, 1965, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Doyle, John; Heff and Wickus, undated, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Drexler, Judge vs. Attorney Schnapp, March 5, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 96-97)
    - Election Special, Carley Interview, January 30, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Election Special, Democrats, with Bronson LaFollette, undated, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Election Special, undated, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Election Special, Housing, March 1965, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Election Wrap Up, with Dick Steinburg and Tom Nelson, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 102-103)
    - Fairchild, Thomas E., Justice, Role of the Wisconsin Supreme Court, February 11, 1966, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 104-105)
    - Fish, Odie, Press Conference, undated, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Fish, Odie Press Conference, Warren Knowles Speaks, undated, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Ford, Republican Fund Raising, undated, Audio reel (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Halloway, Harry vs. Judge Holz, March 28, 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 109-110)
    - Heines, W. Arlene, undated, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Higbee, Selma Interviews, May 1965, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Highlights of the Democratic Convention Held in Milwaukee, May 22, 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Highway Safety, with Wildschut, Duffey and Teicht, June 14, 1965, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Jackson, Patrick Lucey Interview, undated, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Jefferson/Jackson Day Dinner, Democrats, Press Club Debate, May 22, 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Kennedy, Robert Speech, Baker Field House, September 17, 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Knowles Press Conference, June 1965, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Knowles Press Conference, undated, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 119-120)
    - Knowles: Budget Message, January 26, 1967, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - LaFollette, Bronson; Huber and Carley, Introduction to Zafarski; Patrick Lucey, undated, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Lieutenant Governor Race, with Martin J. Schreiber and Jerome Grant, September 11, 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Lieutenant Governor Race, with John Olson, undated, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Lucy, Patrick and Robert Kennedy Dinner, August 15, 1965, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 125-126)
    - McCanley, Lewis L., Warden of Taycheeda Correctional Institution, June 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 127)